# ANDREA HEITON

425.387.0798 | andrea.helton@icloud.com

#### **CUSTOMER SERVICE | ATTENTION TO DETAIL | LEADERSHIP**

Strong customer service personality, with experience in conflict resolution with both guests and employees. Utilized a strong focus in task completion and delegation skills to accomplish desired results.

#### **SKILLS SUMMARY**

### **Highly Organized**

SKILLFULLY MANAGE LARGE PROJECTS, START-TO-FINISH.

#### Resourceful Problem Solver

ADEPT IN ANTICIPATING AND ANALYZING PROBLEMS, THEN FORMULATING SOLUTIONS.

### **Computer Proficiency**

MICROSOFT WORD, EXCEL, POWERPOINT, AND ONE NOTE

# **EXPERIENCE**

### National General Insurance

Everett, WA July 2019-Present

# Customer Care Representative Tier 2

- Answering phone calls following appropriate scripting
- Problem solving to assist customers
- CONTACTING APPROPRIATE DEPARTMENTS TO ASSIST CUSTOMERS
- FOLLOWING QUALITY CONTROL GUIDELINES FOR CALLS

### Tommy Bahama

Tulalip, Wa, 2018–July 2019

# Key-Holder

- PROVIDING SUPPORT AND FEEDBACK TO THE STAFF
- Maintaining displays on sales floor
- RECONCILING THE TILLS

### **EDUCATION**

• Marysville Arts & Technology High School, Marysville, WA

September 2010-June 2014

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA